Guide to the George Mason University photograph collection, 1950s-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: University Relations, 1950s-1999; (37 boxes)
  - James Dickey, May 05, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Campus building, May 06, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Students on quad, May 08, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Library, faculty, May 09, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Reception, etc., May 12, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - George W. Johnson, May 16, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Sports award, May 17, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Headshots, county court house, May 17, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - African objects, May 18-20, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Art exhibit, May 19, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, May 21, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Woman in wheelchair, May 23, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Meetings, May 23, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Dance, May 24, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Reception, nursing, May 25, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Vernon Spence, May 27, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Softball, frisbee, etc., May 28-29, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Piano, etc., June 05, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Construction, June 10, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Rainy day, cemetery, June 11, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Softball, June 12, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Groundbreaking (Robinson Hall), June 14, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Registration, June 15, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Robert Krug, June 16-17, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Horticulture, portraits, June 18, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Students, library, Donald Mash, etc., July 2-8, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - George Johnson, July 09, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Donald Mash, Ralph Roberts, et al, July 11, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Campus scenes, July 12, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Donald Mash, Carol Sudal, et al, July 13 -15, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Monkeys, July 16, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Dart game, July 26, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Students, July 27, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Teaching, July 27, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Frisbee, George Johnson, etc., July 28, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Portraits, August 01, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Students, August 02, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Classroom, portraits, August 3-8, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Northern Virginia Writers Project, August 9-11, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Cross country runners, August 10, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - African robe (Liberian), August 12, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Reception, August 13-14, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Campus scenes, August 15-16, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Butcher, August 19, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Registration, August 19, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Campus scenes, students, dorms, bookstore, etc., August 20-25, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Capitol, GMU students, August 26, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Campus scenes, August 27-29, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Construction, etc., August 30, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Campus, table tennis, September 30, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Show rehersal, October 01, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Preaching on campus, October 02, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Softball, etc., October 3-6, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Mann maps, October 07, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Library (Kurzweil, African objects, etc.), October 17, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Patriot's Day, October 18, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Martha Turnage, October 20, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Students, October 21, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Back to school conference, October 22, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Campus scenes, October 24-26, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Field trip, October 27, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Students, rugby, motorcycles, dance, November 01, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - John Warner, November 02, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Meeting, Research Center for the Federal Theatre Project, November 04, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Professor, teaching, November 15, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Research Center for the Federal Theatre Project, November 08, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Students, mascot, November 09, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - John Warner, November 10, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Planning meeting, November 11, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Charles Robb, November 15, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Reception, November 17, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - George Johnson, meeting, December 05, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Biology Department, Library, etc., December 10, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Debate, January 05, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Robert Hawkes, January 07, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Commencement, January 12, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Eric Leeper, January 15, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Research Center for the Federal Theatre Project, January 16, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Monkey, etc., January 17-18, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Profesors, January 20, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Art class, etc., January 24, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Town an Country Realtors Scholarship Presentation, January 01, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Snow, February 5-12, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Ron Nessen, reception, February 12-14, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Dance class, February 12, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Popsicles, February 14, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - African art collection, etc., February 14, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Construction [Robinson B], February 16, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - African art collection, February 21, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Monkeys, etc., February 21, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Choreography, February 23, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Forensics/Debate, February 24, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Campus scenes, February 28, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Mary Margaret Greene, March 01, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Contribution to Business School from Chi Omega, March 01, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Governor Dalton, et al (GMU School of Law), March 02, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Library, March 02, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - African art collection, March 03, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Classroom, reception, March 5-6, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Lillian Anthony-Welch, etc., March 07, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Ceremony, March 07, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Campus scenes, March 08, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Construction, March 08, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Library, March 08, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Volleyball, March 09, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Campus scenes, March 12, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Board of Visitors, March 14, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Gloria Steinem, bicycling, etc., March 21, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Bicycling, campus scenes, March 21, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Construction, March 23, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - George Johnson, March 26, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Campus scenes, March 28, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Library, meeting, March 28, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Dance, March 30, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Campus scenes, Peter Henriques-Northern Virginia Heritage, March 30, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Academics, April 03, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Student Apartments housing, April 01, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - George Johnson inauguration, April 07, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Debate team, forensics, April 11, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - George Johnson family, Fall 1979 Class Schedule Cover, April 13, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Robert Krug, Henry Adams, et al, April 17, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - GMU School of Law, April 18, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Counseling center, campus scenes, April 19, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - George Mason Day, April 20, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Consortium, Betty Mann, April 24, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Photography, speech, April 27, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Sports, campus scenes, etc., May 01, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - GMU School of Law, May 02, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Campus scenes, May 03, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Exhibit, campus scenes, May 07, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Coach Spuhler, May 10, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Meeting, May 12, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Governor's tour, May 14, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Campus scenes, May 16, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Jan Cohn, May 17, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Graduation, Joan Briskin, May 19, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - David Powers, Leon Boothe, Mann maps, May 23, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Student Affairs, May 24, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Lab, photography, May 31, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Federal Theatre Project (FTP), June 01, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Dr. Rockwood and bats, June 04, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Photography, etc., June 05, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Portraits, June 06, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Nursing, June 12, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Biology boat, etc, June 13, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Research Center for the Federal Theatre Project, etc., June 15, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Becky Jo Moore, etc., June 21, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Dr. Michael Kelley, Dean's conference, etc., June 26, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - George Johnson, et al, July 02, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Pianist, colonial medicine, July 05, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Public affairs, Planning committee, campus-summer, July 06, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Molka Reich, July 12, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Krug party with George Johnson, July 14, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Library, Chris Walters, Wendy and Ron Levy, July 16 -17, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Professor J. Samuels, et al, July 23, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - WEEL, July 25, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Musical instruments, July 26, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Campus scenes, August 03, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Summer Graduation, August 06, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Academics, etc., August 09, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Reading on lawn, skyscapes, August 20, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Viewbook, Treasure chest, August 27, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - West Springfield High School, DC, Campus Scenes, August 28, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Student Teaching dinner-education, August 30, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Class schedule cover/lab, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - "Year of Child" exhibit, African Art exhibit, September 04, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Olde Town Alexandria, Crowded parking lots, woods scene, Scott Nicholls and Gabrielle Beckman, September 06, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Library and the Humanities Grant, September 08, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Helen Ackerman, Roburt Dumas, copies of Russia, September 10, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Construction, September 11, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Washington DC, Vincent Callahan and Board of Visitors, Federal Theatre Project (FTP), student housing, September 12, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Night class, commuting bus, library, Georgetown, tennis Students, Minority Affairs, bank, September 13, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Dr. Martha Turnage, September 14, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Law school, Eric Leeper, September 18, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Mrs. George W. Johnson (Joanne), September 19, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Dumas reception, September 21, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - President's dinner for Spuhlers, September 23, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Presentation of check, September 24, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Adams reception, September 26, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Dorothy McDiamrmid, October 02, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Gunston Hall/James Ott, October 04, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Rejuvenate your joints, Cardiac rehabilitation, October 08, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Vietnamese donation-J. Veenstra, library, Einstein display, October 10, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Geln Furbush, Roberta Gupta, October 15, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Cross country team, October 16, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - "Good Doctor", October 17, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Scales, October 18, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Children playing doctor, David Powers,Coleman/C.Jones/drum, Patriots Day, October 19, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Senator Hayakaura, Mosby exhibit, Am. Dick Clark, October 24, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Cozzens, Cohelan, John Victor, October 26, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Dr. Levy/Dr. Chu/North Campus, Jacobs/Levy/Gloria Fauth, October 30, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - North Campus, Norma Jean Reception/Maurice Scherrens, October 31, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - WRQX/ Warren Yaeger, Modern dance, November 01, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Biology Department/John Victor, St. Georges, November 02, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Alumni director/ Dr. Morgan, November 07, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Northern Virginia Writer's Conference, November 07, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Adm. Coleman, Coleman/Bennett/Johnson, November 13, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Consumer and the law, November 14, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Pennington/ Inst. Analysis, Coat of Arms (Mason), November 16, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Consortium, November 27, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Tom Bass/Leon Boothe, Legislative dinner, November 29, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Virginia Square station, December 01, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Forensics, December 03, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Betly Mann (Mrs. C. Harrison Mann), December 04, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Daisies/Potpourri, December 05, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Board of Visitors, December 17, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Moot Court winner, President's Christmas party, December 19, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Activities, students, 1980s (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Aerial shots of campus, 1980s (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Art class, 1980s (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Athletics, 1980s (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Cadmus-Law school, 1980s (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Campus scenes, 1980s (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Donna Bafundo-Director of Summer Session, 1980s (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Dr. Rita Carty-Nursing, 1980s (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - George Andrykovitch-Biology, 1980s (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Gordon Bradley-Mens soccer coach, 1980s (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Graduation (black and colored prints), 1980s (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Johnson Center construction and completion (black and colored prints), 1980s (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Robinson professors, 1980s (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - School of Law award, 1980s (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Shaul Bakhash - Robinson professor, 1980s (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Vassily Aksyonov, 1980s (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Portraits, 1980s-1990s (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Mary Bateson-Robinson Professor Anthropology, 1980s-1992 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Richard Bausch-English, 1980s-1995 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Lawrence Bowen-Educatoin and Public Policy; Enterprise Hall, 1980s-1996 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Dr. James Buchanan portraits and miscellaneous, 1980s-1999 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - President George W. Johnson, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Stanley/Ryan, January 08, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Graduation, January 12, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Johnston/McKee, January 17, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Summer catalog, January 23, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Dean Boothe reception, January 24, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Board of Visitors/Alumni, January 25, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Rainey/Clarke, Andrews/Tombes, January 28, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Tombes, Security, Briskin, Bennett, Johnson, Snavely, Bowen, January 29, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Dr. MacConkey, J. Cohn, Board of Trustees, January 30, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Olan tunji, February 01, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Anita Taylor, February 04, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Rainey/Bowen/Briskin, Coperly/ Lankford, Noah, February 05, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Robert Garmer, February 06, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Anthony-Welch, Homecoming, February 09, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Arts, reception, February 09, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - GMU Law School, February 13, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Robert Epskamp, February 14, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Dr. Jack Savage, February 18, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Gantz/ Stopp/ MacConkey, George Walker, Medievalist Guild, February 20, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Congressman Joseph L. Fisher, February 21, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Modern dance, February 26, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Moot Court/Isenberg, Master dance, snow scenes, Senta Driver, March 04, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Harsh/Oppelt/Snavely/Hecht, March 06, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Erlich, Walter, Fletcher, Walker, Mellinger, March 10, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - C.Wilhelmi, Athletic Building bid, March 13, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - "House of Blue Leaves", March 17, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - M. Spikell, J. Scimecca, March 18, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - International week, March 20, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Fedderman/Porush, Goodwin/Cooper, Class schedule, Reynolds/White/Shreve, Clifton, Writers Conference, March 27, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Personnel orientation, April 01, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Russell Duke, Richard Entrikin, Peter Millspaugh, Irwin Greenberg, Robert Johnston, April 02, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Groundbreaking, Outdoor scenes, University Day, C. Wilhelmi, April 07, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Harold Brown, David Cushing, April 10, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Dick Gregory, April 11, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Mike Sundell, etc., April 14, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - John Victor, etc., April 18, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Forensics, April 21, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Martin Agronsky, Russell Nye/FTP puppet, outdoor scenes, April 27-29, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Mary Cho/FTP, April 30, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Terry Hollman, etc., May 01, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Trap and skeet, May 02, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Student awards, May 03, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Judy Pelham/BIS/Art room, Sunrise, May 08, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Student handbook/personnel, ROTC signing, May 12, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - SUB personnel/ handbook, May 13, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Board of Visitors/Ken Haggerty, L. Anthony-Welch, May 14, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Bob Hamalton-Midas, May 16, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Graduation, May 17, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Reception/Alumni awards, May 17, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - George Mason Bank donation, May 22, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Barbara Given, May 29, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Staff picnic, June 01, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Alumni awards, June 03, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Molka Reich, June 04, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Bulldozer, June 09, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Orientation, June 12, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Plans, nursing lab, Lee Cook, doctoral students, orientation, June 13, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Robinson luncheon, Chemistry lab, June 19, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Johnson/McGrady/signs, June 26, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Joan Briskin, Quita Craig Luncheon, sunrise, June 27, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - New member party, July 01, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Campus, security/traffic regulation, July 07, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Campus, security, July 10 -11, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Black orientation, July 13, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Marianne Lattell, Refugee conference, July 15, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Wolf Trap chorus, Doctor of Arts/ B.Beyer, July 17, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Leon Jaworski, Gov. Dalton (?), July 20, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - GMU School of Lawith construction, July 29, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Biology class/Library, July 30, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Graduation, August 09, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Robinson II/Science lab/Dean DeBoer/Library moving and construction, August 14, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - President's house, Black student on campus, August 15, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Campus and wildlife, CUE Bus service ribbon cutting, August 18, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Italian visitors, biology lab, green house, caterpillar, August 19, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Connie Bedell-Board of Visitors, August 20, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Moving into Robinson Hall II/ Science lab, August 21, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Joe Harrington/pipe organ/ Robinson II, August 22, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Black and white interacting, August 26, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Professor Yance moving, August 28, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Stephanie Hopkins, September 04, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - George Johnson, Stephanie Hopkins, Honor Roll II, etc., September 05, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - James Smith, Bill Cohn, September 08, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Connie Bedell, September 09, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Lisa McGrady/White House, September 10, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Chinese visitors, September 12, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Henry Lampe, September 15, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - State of the University Address, September 17, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Rhymers, September 19, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Basketball, September 22, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Forensics, Carren Roberts, September 22, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Carren Roberts/Boneau, Honor Roll II, etc., September 30, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Mrs. Joanne Johnson's party, concert, October 05, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Hirst donation, October 06, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Lisa McGrady, Campus, D. Mash in wheelchair, October 08, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Patriot's Day, October 10, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Reception, October 12, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Book sorting, Glenn and Shearer, October 21, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Board of Trustees, book donation, October 22, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Joe Harrington, PE Building, Business Society (n), October 23, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Friends of the library, October 23, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Mills donation/choral, book sale, October 24, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Master dance, October 26, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Justice Powell/ Law School, October 27, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - John Jones/ Walter Williams, Dance, October 28, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Shadow Box, October 29, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Patriot's club reception, old and new Board of Visitors, November 03, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Mills donation, November 04, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Chinese visitors/ Biology Department, November 07, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Board/ Board of Visitors, November 12, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Arnold Lobel, November 14, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - John Cole (Public Affairs Department), November 19, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Gunston Hall, November 22, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - International Day, November 23, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Consortium, November 25, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Susan McCormick, December 03, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Cheerleaders/ Carla Garrell, December 04, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Studio Theatre dedication with Helen Hill Miller, December 05, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - R. Bausch, vandalism, Black scholars, incentive grant reception, December 08, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Christmas concert-Jim Smith, December 10, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Joseph Gittler (sociology), Incentive grant reception, December 11, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Alumni office-Homecoming, Northern VA writing project, December 12, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Christmas party, December 19, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Gunston Hall 18th Century Christmas, December 20, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Lecture, January 07, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - George Mason Stamp ceremony at Gunston Hall, June 03, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - African art collection, commencement, etc., January 13, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - COG computer ridesharing, Dr. Judith Jacobs, yearbook Staff, etc., January 15, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Summer catalog, parking lot, etc., January 21, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Northern Virginia (VA) Writing Project, January 30, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 24)